-大家好 -晚上好 伙计们
- Hi. - Evening, folks.
-进去吧 -你好
- Come on in. - Hi.
等等 等一下 各位 等等
Wait, wait! Hang on, guys! Wait!
你不用查身份证吗
Don't you need to check I.D.s?
-对对对 -要查要查
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Huh?
抱歉 我们没有老年人折扣
Sorry, we don't offer a senior discount.
不不 不是因为我
No. No, it's not for me,
现在我真得喝一杯了
and now I really need a drink.
来吧 亲爱的 给他看你的驾照
Go on, honey. Show him your license. Go on.
-拍照 -有人恰好今天年满21岁吗
- Picture! -Oh? Somebody 21 today?
-是啊 -还是女兵呢
- Yes. Yes. - Military gal.
欢迎光临 二等兵多切斯特
Welcome, Private Dorchester.
拿错了
That is the wrong one.
很抱歉
I am so very sorry.
-稍等 -相机收起来
- Hold on a second. - Put that away!
我知道 跟家里人
Yes, I'm a huge dork
一起庆祝21岁生日真是蠢透了
for celebrating my 21st with my family,
但我妈疯了似的非要带我去酒吧
But my mom was crazy excited to go to a bar with me.
也可能只是她自己想去
Or just to go to a bar.
你俩这么做太有爱了
Aw, it's so nice what you two are doing.
我妈就不会带我出来喝酒
My mother would have never taken me out for a drink.
为什么 她非常严格吗
Why? Was she super strict?
不是 是她从不把我当大人看
No, she would never see me as an adult.
当然 除了警察来家里
Well, except when the police came to the house.
那时她就会说
then, she would be like,
歌洛莉亚 你去跟他们谈
"Gloria, you go talk to them.
告诉他们你父亲昨晚在家
"Tell them your father was here last night.
不过你要先解开几个上衣扣子
But unbutton your shirt a little bit first."
好吧 这是我听过最疯狂的事情
Okay, uh, the craziest thing I heard --
这下有的比了
and there is some competition there --
你觉得这位女士把我当大人看了吗
is that you think this lady treats me like I'm an adult.
等等 我真的把你当大人了啊
Wait, I-I do treat you like an adult.
我们出发之前 你还让我换了两次衣服
You made me change my shirt two times before we left the house
还逼我吃了个芝士三明治
and force-fed me a cheese sandwich
免得我喝得烂醉
so I wouldn't get sloppy drunk.
那只是一个女人向另一个女人提供一些
No, that is just one woman offering another woman, uh,
关于时尚和休闲饮酒的建议
fashion tips and advice for casual drinking.
你对时尚了解多少
What do you know about fashion?
对休闲饮酒又了解多少
What do you know about casual drinking?
好了好了 真好笑
Okay, okay. That's funny.
你看 放到以前 我就不会笑了
See, I wouldn't have laughed
因为那时候你还是个孩子
at that before 'cause you were a kid,
但现在我会笑了 因为真的很好笑
but now I'm gonna laugh 'cause it's funny.
抱歉让你们等了这么久
Hi. Sorry that took so long.
我们被那边那帮伴娘困住了
We got trapped by those bridesmaids over there.
-是啊 -你好
- Yeah. - Hi.
带基佬来
That's what happens
异性恋酒吧玩就是这样
when you bring gay guys to a straight club.
对喝醉的开单身派对的姑娘来说
We're like catnip to drunken
我们就是醒酒剂
bachelorette party girls.
问题就是 她们有点粘人
The problem is, they can get a little bit clingy.
但别担心 我们今晚是为你来的
But don't worry, haley. We are here for you tonight.
为海莉人生中的第一杯酒 干杯
To Haley's first drink, huh? Salud.
-来吧 -来吧
-Okay. - Yeah. Yeah.
好辣呀
Ooh, it burns.
再次感谢你载我 杰
Thanks again for driving me, Jay.
您已到达您的目的地
You've arrived at your destination.
懂吗 因为我们开的是德国汽车
Get it? 'cause we're in a German car.
我已经渡过了漫长又充实的一生
I have lived a long, full life.
我会开车撞墙上的
I will drive us into a wall.
今晚 克莱尔先带着大家去酒吧庆祝
Tonight, while Claire gets things started at the bar,
杰则带着我去取海莉的生日礼物
Jay is taking me to pick up Haley's birthday present --
一辆新车
A new car!
菲尔总是货比三家 然后挑既安全
Phil shopped around, found something very safe
保养费用低 评价又好的东西
and low-maintenance with lots of good reviews.
直到我娶了她
Till I married her.
我开玩笑呢 你的保养费用可不低
I'm joking! You're not low-maintenance!
-我双重打击成功 -我懂你意思
- I doubled down. - Oh, I heard you.
你确定你不用我陪你进去吗
Are you sure you don't want me to go in with you,
也许还能敲定一些细节
you know, maybe hammer out some final details?
不用 协议已经订好了
No. Deal's already worked out.
我只需用我灵活的手指
I'm just gonna pop my
在几份表格上签个字
Herbie Hancock on a few forms,
我们 我们酒吧见
and I'll, uh -- I'll meet you at the bar.
太好了 你不用我陪
Great. Well, you don't need me.
把菲尔丢给汽车销售员
Leaving Phil with a car salesman
就好比将一只涂满烧烤酱的小山羊
is like covering a baby goat in barbecue sauce
丢到塞伦盖蒂平原上
and dropping it in the middle of the Serengeti.
我 好像一切都 等等
Well, I-it all seems to check -- wait a minute.
不对劲儿啊
This can't be right.
我可以用红笔签字吗
Am I allowed to sign this with a red pen?
说得对 菲尔
Good catch, Phil.
一个小问题 如果你真的想为女儿
One quick thing -- if you really want to
准备一份特别的礼物
do something special for your daughter,
要不要考虑给车装上升级版轮胎
what do you say we throw in some upgraded wheels?
要多少钱
How much would that cost?
你一天在一杯咖啡上花多少钱
How much do you spend a day on a cup of coffee?
看在老天的份上
Oh, for god's sakes!
-杰 -回答问题
- Jay? - Answer the question!
一杯咖啡 3.5美元
A cup of coffee? $3.50.
-不是你 -你进来干什么
- Not you! - What are you doing here?
我来确保一切都是光明磊落的
I'm just here to make sure everything's on the up-and-up.
达里尔 这是我岳父杰·普里契特
Um, Daryl, this is my father-in-law, Jay Pritchett.
杰 你没必要过来
Jay, you don't have to be here.
一切都解决了
It's all worked out.
这样吧 不如你加上
Tell you what, why don't you throw in
你很喜欢的升级版轮胎
those upgraded wheels you love so much,
再降价五百元 我们成交
lower the drive-off by $500, we call it a deal?
抱歉 但这是最优惠的价格了
I'm sorry, but this is the best I can do.
拜托 达里尔 我们都是生意人
Come on, Daryl. We're all businessmen here.
我们都知道虽然我们说
We all know there's wiggle room
没有降价空间 但实际上是有的
when we say there's no wiggle room.
所以赶紧的 你降价吧[摇摆]
So, come on. Let's see you wiggle.
我做不到 我不能降价[摇摆]
I can't. I can't wiggle.
杰 我已经让他降价了
Jay, I've already wiggled him.
不 相信我 他能降价
No, trust me, he can wiggle.
我真的做不到
I really can't. I --
降价 达里尔 降价
Wiggle, Daryl. Wiggle.
你知道孩子是从哪里来的吗
Do you know where babies come from?
莉莉 我在学习
Lily, I'm studying.
你是个书呆吗
Are you a nerd?
不是 你为什么这么问我
No. Why would you ask me that?
现在是周五晚上 你却在做作业
It's Friday night, and you're doing homework.
我都高三了
It's my senior year.
相信我 莉莉
Trust me, Lily,
我以后会过上很多有趣的周五之夜
there'll be tons of fun Friday nights in my future
跟画家 政要和其他科学家们一起
with artists, dignitaries, other scientists.
我没听到"男朋友"
I didn't hear "Boyfriend."
3次命中0次 你一直在打我的脸
You're 0 for 3. You keep hitting me in the face.
或者 我三次都命中了
Or...am I 3 for 3?
那苹果还有什么意义
Then what's the point of the apple?
可以让你不乱动
It keeps you from moving.
各位 你们知道孩子是从哪里来的吗
Hey, guys, do you know where babies come from?
莉莉 这问题不合适
Lily, that's not an appropriate question.
拜托 你到底知不知道
Come on. Do you know or not?
知道 怀孕带来的
Uh, yes. The stork brings them.
这个笨蛋吗[音似]
This dork?
好笑
Good stuff.
莉莉 想吃点什么吗
Hey, Lily, how about something to eat?
你要吃鸡块吗
You want some chicken nuggets?
-好的 -好
- Okay. - All right.
你知道孩子是怎么来的吗
So, do you know how babies are made?
是的 我会告诉你
Yep, and I'll tell you.
但首先 我们需要一支笔
But first, we're gonna need a pen
和一个贝果饼
and a bagel.
为什么
Why?
你需要记笔记 而我饿了
Well, you're gonna need to take notes, and I'm hungry.
拜托
Please.
好了 我们不能再等了
Okay, we can't wait any longer.
我们迫不及待要给出礼物了
We are dying to give you our present!
各位 我说了不要礼物的
Guys, I said no gifts.
不 你是说不要一百元以下的礼物
No, you said no gifts under $100.
是吗 给我
Oh, did I? Gimme.
是你超酷的基舅们的一点小心意
It's just a little something from your supercool guncles.
好吧
Okay!
这种事压力很大的 基佬舅舅...
There is a lot of pressure when one is a gay uncle...
或者说基舅
Or guncle.
要送海莉这么潮的侄女一份礼物
...giving a gift to a niece as hip and chic as Haley.
我们在一起的十年里
In the 10 years that we've been together,
只有一次搞砸了
we've only missed the mark one time.
那次克莱尔告诉了我们该买什么
Yeah, when Claire told us what to buy,
但我们学到了教训
but we learned our lesson --
无视克莱尔 相信我们的基佬直觉
Ignore Claire and trust our gay instincts.
或者说"基觉"
Or "Ginstincts."
太过了
Too much.
别说了
No.
天啊 好可爱
Oh, my god! So cute!
-你真这么觉得吗 -是啊 超可爱
- Really? You think? - Yes! Totally! Super cute!
如果你不喜欢的话 我们可以退掉的
Because we can return them if you don't like them.
不不 挺好的
No, no, they're good.
我喜欢
I love them.
如果我们穿同一码的鞋子
If we wore the same size,
我现在就会穿上
I would have these on right now.
他走开很长时间了
He's been gone a long time.
我觉得我们伤害了他的感情
I think we hurt his feelings.
这些人没感情
These guys don't have feelings.
他在后面勾搭秘书呢
He's back there making time with a secretary,
吹嘘自己带了几个白痴去试驾
bragging about how he's taking a couple suckers for a ride.
瞧 他之前是军人
Look. He was in the military.
奥斯瓦德也是[肯尼迪遇刺案的主凶]
So was Oswald.
你能信任我
Can you trust me
会给你争取到最优惠的价格吗
that I'm gonna get you the best deal possible?
知道吗
You know what?
为什么我要一直抗拒你
Why do I keep fighting you on this?
你知道自己在做什么
You know what you're doing.
我会一直跟随你的
I'm behind you all the way.
我跟经理谈过了
Well, I spoke to my manager...
怎么样
Yeah.
轮胎或者折扣都没法给你们
...and I can't give you the wheels or the discount.
说实话
Frankly, he's mad
我给你的那个价格让他很不满
that I gave you the deal that's on the table.
谢谢 达里尔 你尽力了
Well, thanks, Daryl. You did your best.
你也是 杰
You, too, Jay.
我还是签了然后赶紧开走吧
I guess we'll just sign and be on our way.
-我们还是走吧 -什么
- Or we can get out of here. - What?
对不起 老兄
I'm sorry, buddy.
他家附近的经销商那里有我一个哥们
I got a pal at the dealership closer to his house.
我们去那买好了 菲尔 我们走
We're gonna take our business there. Let's go, Phil.
我觉得菲尔想买下这辆车
I think Phil wants to take the car.
不用你告诉菲尔他想干什么
Don't tell Phil what he wants.
菲尔想走了
Phil wants to leave.
菲尔
Phil?
我们在干什么 那个价格已经很低了
What are we doing? That was a great deal.
错 别停下
Wrong. Keep walking.
杰 我需要这辆车
Jay, I need this car.
二十分钟内我们就要赶到酒吧去
We're supposed to be at the bar in 20 minutes.
淡定 他不会让我们离开这里的
Calm down. He's not gonna let us leave the lot.
你现在点一杯苹果马提尼
You can order your Appletini now
等你到酒吧的时候冰都不会化的
and be there before the ice melts.
买车这事上你最好是对的
You better be right about this
因为苹果马提尼里根本没有冰
'cause you are dead wrong about Appletinis having ice.
伙计们 等一下
Hey! Guys, hold on a second!
什么事 达里尔
Yes, Daryl.
你忘记拿墨镜了
You forgot your sunglasses.
开心啦
Happy?
是的
Yeah.
这不是我的墨镜
These aren't my sunglasses.
真不敢相信海莉不喜欢那双鞋
I cannot believe Haley didn't like the shoes.
别这么想 她当然喜欢了
Oh, come on. Of course she did.
不 我很确定她不喜欢 她用了高音
No, she most certainly did not. She gave us the high voice.
"好可爱啊"
"They're cute!"
我知道那音调
I know the voice.
那音调是我发明的 我常用的
I invented the voice. I use the voice.
等等 这么说我不适合穿中长裤吗
Wait. So, I can't pull off mid-thigh shorts?
不 你可以
No, you can.
你可以脱下来送给比你年轻二十岁的人
Pull them off and give them to somebody 20 years younger.
你可真傻
You're so silly!
你们俩在笑什么
What are you two giggling about?
海莉刚才问我
Haley just asked me --
你不会想知道的 相信我
Oh, you don't want to know, trust me.
不 我想 我想知道 告诉我
No, I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. Tell me.
不 你又会评头论足了
No, you'll just be all judgy
因为你希望我是个完美的小天使
because you want me to be this perfect, little angel.
宝贝 不 不是那样的
Oh, honey, no, that's not true.
我知道 目前为止我做得不是很好
I know I have not done a great job of it so far,
但是我是真心的
but I meant it when I said
我希望跟你的关系更成人化
I want to have a more adult relationship.
我很肯定 我和妈
I am sure the reason
产生隔阂的原因就是
why mom and I grew apart
她一直把我当孩子来对待
is that she never stopped treating me like a child.
而且她就是让疯狂朱古力泡芙发疯的原因
Plus, she was loco for Loco-puffs.
怎么 你们都没吃过那种麦片吗
What, you do not have that cereal?
海莉 告诉我
Come on. Haley, let me in.
好吧 我们刚才笑
Okay, fine, so we were laughing
是因为我们在玩"你选哪个"的游戏
because we were playing "Would you rather."
那是什么游戏
What's that?
我说
And I said,
你选嫁给乔治·克鲁尼
"Would you rather marry George Clooney
还是跟汤姆·哈迪滚一次这辈子
"or have the best sex of your life for just one night
最棒的床单
with Tom Hardy?"
-那是谁 -不知道 上网搜一下
- Who's that? - I don't know. Google him.
我选汤姆 因为乔治只会
I'm going with Tom because George would
喋喋不休地谈论政治
just want to talk about politics all the time
而汤姆看起来会安静地把事办完
and Tom seems like he would quietly get the job done.
海莉说了一模一样的话
That's exactly what Haley said!
-好吧 -是的
- All right! Okay! - Yeah!
你们俩 来跳舞
Hey, you two! It's dance time!
天哪 又来了
Oh, boy. Here we go.
是啊 看来有人还不满足哦
Yeah, somebody's hungry for a little bit more.
应该告诉她们我们是直男
We should have just told them we're straight.
我们认识她们就是因为
We met them because you accurately
你准确地闻出了新娘的香水品牌
identified the bride's perfume.
你们两个准备好扭动起来了吗
You two ready to tear it up?
我们现在正忙自己的事呢
Oh... Well, we're kind of doing our own thing right now,
-不过谢谢邀请 -来吧 小伙子们
- but thank you. - Come on, boys!
那两个基佬哪儿来的
Who are those gays?
我不知道 不过我喜欢他们的长相
I don't know, but I like their look.
-是吗 -真的吗
- Do you? - Really?
是的
Yeah.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
这个人会给我们想要的价格
This guy's gonna get us the deal we want.
我想要的价格曾经就摆在我面前
I had the deal we want,
现在没了
and now it's gone,
就像你幻想的
just like your
那个没在这里工作过的朋友一样
imaginary friend who never worked here.
淡定 我们已经赚到
Calm down. We're already up
三个热狗和一副墨镜了
three hot dogs and a pair of sunglasses.
两位 我仔细算了一下
Okay, guys, I ran some numbers,
我们给不了那家店给你们的价格
and I can't come close to the price you had over there.
对方的价格已经亏本了
He was losing money on that car.
-不是吧 -这样没用
- Oh, my God. - Not helping.
行了 托尼 我们废话少说
All right, Tony, let's cut to the chase.
要么我们开始谈价格
You either start negotiating,
要么我们就回人家那里买了
or we're gonna walk back over there and take that other deal.
要是你还能拿到那个价的话
Well, if you can still get it,
赶紧去吧 换我也会那么做
yeah, th-that's what I would do.
你想这么玩吗
You want to dance.
好 我不介意 我先来
I don't mind. I'll lead.
给我便宜五百元
$500 down.
先生 就算是在吃热狗马拉松
Sir even with the deep discounts we offer
大促销期间
during the hot dog-a-thon,
我也没见过那么低的价格
I have never seen a deal like that.
听到没 杰
Hear that, Jay?
我赢了 赢了什么
I won. What did I win?
反正不是一辆车
Not a car!
我得去给刚刚那个销售员打电话
I got to call that first guy back.
托尼 倒计时进行中 轮到你了
Tony, clock is ticking. Your move.
那是什么
What's that?
是你们经理说什么了吗
Could that be from your manager, huh, perhaps?
对 他说你要是不买车
Uh, yeah, he says that unless you buy a car,
就不能再吃热狗了
you can't have any more hot dogs.
好 有一对男女在兄弟会派对上认识了
Okay, so, a boy and a girl meet at a frat party
他们都觉得对方超辣的
and they both think each other is totally hot,
所以他们喝完啤酒之后就上楼了
so they pound their beers and head upstairs.
卢克 别说了
Luke, stop.
她不能跟你学这些东西
She's not hearing this from you.
-为什么不能 -你太不成熟了
- Why not? - You're too immature.
我才没有不成熟 你个猪头
I'm not immature, butt face.
换了你会怎么说
And how would you say it?
换我会说他们是通过朋友认识的
Well, I would say they meet through friends,
约会过一段时间之后
and after dating for an appropriate amount of time,
他把她带去一间浪漫的法国餐厅
he takes her to a romantic french bistro.
-然后有可能 来了兴致 -有可能
- Then maybe, if the mood is right -- - maybe?
我刚请你吃了一顿法国大餐
I just bought you a big french dinner.
你自己愿意的 我不欠你
That was your choice. I owe you nothing.
你的手一直都放在我的膝盖上
Your hand was on my knee the whole time.
我该怎么想
What was I supposed to think?
我只是在表达感情 又不是在签合同
I was expressing affection, not signing a contract.
约会到此为止
This date is over.
不是吧 性感宝贝儿 别这样
Come on, sexy. Don't be like that.
跟我生个孩子吧
Make a baby with me.
你们这是在干什么
What is going on in here?!
没什么
Nothing.
我能说很高兴她们没来找我们吗
Can I just say that I'm glad they didn't come get us?
没错 谁想要那种黏人的小妞儿
Exactly. Who needs those clingy broads?
"小妞儿" 这年头还有人用这个词吗
"Broads"? Does anyone say "Broads" anymore?
我不知道 我就说出来试试看
I don't know. I was trying something.
也许她们是看到我们跟海莉她们一起
You know, maybe they just saw us with Haley and they were like,
所以想给我们留点空间
"Hey, let's give those guys some space."
或者他们本来就认识
Or they already knew those gays.
或者她们觉得那些年轻人
Or they thought those young guys
舞跳得比我们好
would be better dancers than us.
不 从何时开始年轻意味着更好了
No, no. Since when does young equal better?
给她们见识一下我们的实力
Oh. Let's show them what we got.
先问一下 我们有什么实力
Hey, real quick... what have we got?
我会做"掀房顶"和"扒白菜"舞蹈动作
Um, well, I can raise the roof and do the cabbage patch.
我会做《单身女士》里那种手势
Okay, and I can do the "Single lady" hand thing.
脖子也得动起来
Yeah, but put your neck into it
不然看起来就像女王在挥手
or you just look like the queen waving.
-说得对 -好了 你准备好了
- Oh, good point. - Okay. Now you're ready.
好吧 我们上
Okay, let's go.
-女士们你们好 -单身女士你们好
- Hey, ladies! - Hey, single ladies!
你们好
Hey, guys!
感谢上帝 我们得脱身了
Oh, thank God. We need to tap out.
对啊 这些小妞太缠人了都不让我们走
Yeah, these chicks latched on and won't let go.
你知道她们总是这样缠着我们
You know how they are with us.
不 你不用告诉我们
No, you don't have to tell us.
我们今晚也没法摆脱那边三个
We couldn't get rid of those three all night.
所以你们何不趁机溜走
So, why don't you guys go ahead and split?
我们帮你们顶上
We'll take over.
-你们确定吗 -对啊 快走吧
- Are you sure? - Yeah, yeah, yeah. Go, go.
-当然 当然 -谢谢
- Yes. Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. - Thank you.
-都交给我们吧 -就是
- We'll hold it down. - Yeah, yeah.
男孩们 你们要去哪里
Boys, where are you going?!
-你们别走 -别担心 女士们
- You guys, don't go! - Oh, yeah, don't worry about it, ladies,
因为我们来了 来一起扭扭
because we are here now and we are ready to boogie.
太好了
Great!
太有意思了
So fun!
我们要去夜店了
We're gonna go hit some clubs now.
夜店 听起来很有趣
Oh, clubs. That sounds rad.
-很酷耶 -就是
- Cool. Super dope. - Yes.
你们玩得开心
You guys have fun.
怎么了
What happened?
我的天
Oh, my God.
别跳了 我们已经过时了
Stop. We're gancient.
说真的 迪伦吗
Really? Dylan?
-迪伦 -是啊 跟你发誓
- Dylan? - Yep. Swear it.
简直不敢相信
Like you cannot believe.
我现在好像有点懂了
You know what? I kind of get him now.
-是吧 -没错
- Right? - Yes!
我一直都很懂迪伦
I always got Dylan.
小心点 你算是我外婆了
Careful. You're like my grandma.
外婆
Grandma?
小心点 我还捅过更亲密的家属呢
Easy. I have stabbed closer relatives than you.
真不敢相信我在和我妈说这些
I can't believe I'm talking to my mom about this.
宝贝 我说过了
Honey, I told you,
你已经是个成年人了
you're a grown-up now.
我会尊重你的选择
I'm gonna respect your decisions,
让你过自己的生活
and let you live your life.
这是我在你21岁生日里
It's the best gift I can give to you
能给你的最好的礼物
on your 21st birthday,
友谊 以及无条件的包容
my friendship and unconditional acceptance.
知道这些对我来说真是太重要了
That means so much to me right now.
-你知道为什么吗 -为什么
- You know why? - Why?
因为我今晚想去纹身
Because I want to get a tattoo tonight,
但是我怕你不同意
and I was afraid you'd say no.
她跟你说了这么多
How could she say no
怎么可能会不同意呢
after everything she just said to you?!
我怎么能不同意呢 有办法吗
How could I say no? Is there a way?
天哪 妈 这是你送我的最好的礼物
Oh, my God, mom, this is the best present ever!
今晚还能更棒吗
Could tonight get any better?!
能啊 她可以替你付钱
Yes! She can pay for it
这样你就可以纹个大的了
so you can get a really big one!
我太激动了
I'm so excited!
菲尔 你在哪 你得赶紧过来
Phil, where are you? You have to get down here
不然海莉就要纹身了
and stop Haley from getting a tattoo.
你说什么 快阻止她啊
What, no, you stop her!
我阻止不了
I can't.
我答应了要做她的朋友
I made a commitment to being her friend.
你为什么要那样做
Why would you do that?
我也不知道 就是想尝试些新事物
I don't know. I was trying something.
开着新车过来 可以分散她的注意力
Just get down here with that car, and we can distract her.
我倒是想啊
I'd love to,
但是你爸一直在耍强硬手段
but your dad played hardball
我没买到车
and we lost it.
你怎么会让这种事发生呢
How on earth did you let that happen?!
我不知道 你怎么不去问问
I don't know. Why don't you ask
海莉脖子上那只小鸟
the tweety bird on Haley's neck?
天哪 别纹在脖子上
Oh, God, not the neck.
她这样已经很难找到工作了
She's a tough-enough hire as it is.
你去处理车的事 我去处理纹身的事
Fine, y-you deal with the car. I'll deal with the tattoo.
快点过来
Just get here.
接下来我们要这么做
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
不 我已经听够你的唠叨了
No, no, no, no. I'm done listening to you.
曾经有一份美好的折扣摆在我面前
I had a great deal.
你知道我怎么知道的吗
You know how I know?
当你还在吃第三个热狗的时候
I called the salesman at the first dealership
我打给第一家代理店的销售员
while you were sneaking your third hot dog,
车子已经卖出去了
and it already sold.
没关系 反正我们也不要那辆车
Fine. We don't need it.
接下来
Here's the plan,
我们就说海莉病得很重
we tell them Haley is really sick.
天哪 你真有病
Oh, my God, you're sick.
真聪明 应该说是我病了
Good thinking! I'll be sick
因为没人关心见不到的人
cause nobody cares about people they can't see.
我已经在网上查了好几周的信息
I researched that car online for weeks,
接着你自以为是地插进来一脚
and then you swoop in with your tough-guy swagger
教我怎么在70年代买车
to teach me a lesson about buying cars in the 70s!
这一切都是你的错
You know, this all happened because of you,
坐在那 一句话也不敢说
sitting there, covered in sweat and fear,
还拆我的台
undercutting my every word.
你要真想拿到好的折扣
Now, if you want a really good deal,
你就给我待在这里 继续上你的网
you park your butt out here, play on your internet.
我要按老方法来
I'm going old-school on this sales weasel,
而且我会杀他个片甲不留
and I'm gonna break him in half.
有人接待你们吗
Is somebody helping you?
你最好拿下他
He better be!
有 谢谢你
Yes, thank you so much.
今晚是我当家
Okay, I am technically in charge tonight,
所以谁都不准告诉莉莉
so no one tells Lily
孩子是怎么来的
where babies come from.
不能同意更多
I could not agree more.
我搞不懂你们美国人为什么
I don't know why you Americans
谈到性就这么紧张
are so uptight about sex.
性对于年轻人来说是充满迷惑的
Sex is confusing for young people,
她不需要从两个胡子都没长全的
and she doesn't need to learn from two fuzz-staches
小屁孩那里知道这些
who barely know anything themselves.
不好意思 你应该看看
Excuse me, you might want to
我的网页浏览记录
check my browser history.
我已经做了不少研究
I've done some research.
真好 现在我只想吐一辈子
Oh. Well, great. I'm just gonna go vomit forever now.
你们在干什么
What are you guys doing?
-没什么 -就在聊天而已
- Nothing. -Just talking.
没什么特别的
Not really anything.
我们能把话说完吗
Can we finish our conversation?
不行 莉莉 抱歉 如果你有问题
No. Lily, I'm sorry, but if you have questions,
只能去问你爸爸们了
you're gonna have to ask your dads.
你们也不知道是不是
You don't know, do you?
-我知道 -我知道
- I do so. - Uh-huh, I know.
不 我们不知道 对不对
No, we don't. Right, guys?
-不知道 -不知道
- No, I guess not. - No.
太丢人了 要我告诉你们不
That's embarrassing. Want me to tell you?
什么
What?
你问我们知不知道小孩是从哪里来的
Hey, that's why you asked if we knew where babies came from --
是因为你想告诉我们吗
Because you wanted to tell us?
是啊 你们都这么大了 该知道了
Yeah, you're old. You should know.
不过你们最好坐下来听我讲
But you might want to sit down for this.
我找到附近的一家纹身店
I found a tattoo shop nearby.
大众点评上四颗星 军人还享有折扣
It has four stars on Yelp, and it has military discount.
二等兵多切斯特前来报到
Well, Private Dorchester reporting for duty.
你今晚真是乐于助人啊 歌洛莉亚
You are just so helpful tonight, Gloria.
-知道你们还该干啥吗 -又有主意了
- You know what else you should do? - Another idea.
你们该弄个母女纹身
You should do mother-and-daughter tattoos,
比如一人纹半个爱心
like -- like, uh, two halves of a heart.
或者星星配月亮
Or the moon and some stars.
或者步枪配小鸟
Or, like, a bird and a rifle.
天啊 就这么办
Oh, my God, let's do that!
不是你说的那种 但可以弄个配对纹身
I mean, not that, but, like, let's get matching tattoos!
我想和你有配对的纹身
I want to do that with you.
-真的吗 -当然
- You do? - Yeah!
那可以成为我们两人
It could be, like, our special thing
这辈子最特殊的东西 只属于你和我
that we have for the rest of our lives, just us.
不管我们去哪里 或是干什么
And no matter where we go or what we do,
别人一问起我们的纹身
when people ask us about our tattoos,
我们可以说它们来自
we can say that they're from
我们生命中最精彩的夜晚
the best night of our lives together.
太美好了
That is so sweet.
我是说真的
I mean it.
我想和你一起纹身 你愿意吗
I want to do it with you. Will you?
不敢相信 但我愿意 我愿意
I can't believe this, but I will. I will.
因为我爱你
I will 'cause I love you.
-我也爱你 -我爱你 我爱你
- I love you, too! - I love you. I love you.
-他们还可以做穿孔 -你够了
- They also have piercing! - Enough.
说句实话吧
You know what?
我其实不需要再当酷哥了
I don't even need to be cool anymore.
有什么意义呢
It's like, why?
是啊 有什么意义呢 谁在乎
Yes, exactly. Why? Who cares.
再说了 不在乎自己酷不酷
Besides, isn't the cooler thing not caring
不是更酷吗
if you're cool?
是啊 如果新的酷是不在乎自己酷不酷
Yeah, and if the new cool is not caring,
那说明我酷到极点 不过我也不在乎
then I'm supercool, not that I care.
猜怎么着 我们要去弄配对纹身了
Hey, guys! Guess what. We're getting matching tattoos.
不错 我们也要 我们需要弄这个
Love it. We're doing it, too. We need this.
-你们认真的吗 -我们认真的吗
- Are you serious? - Are we serious?
像伯特和尔尼一样认真[芝麻街搭档角色]
As serious as Bert and Ernie.
这本该是我作为父亲无比美好的一刻
It was supposed to be such a great moment for me as a dad.
我本该走进那家酒吧
I was gonna walk into that bar,
把新车钥匙交给女儿 对她说
give my daughter her new car keys, and say,
乖女儿
"Honey...
把酒喝完 我们去兜风
Chug that drink. We're going for a spin."
菲尔 把这放到你包包里吧
Phil, put these in your purse.
我把你说砍不下来的价往下砍了500元
I just beat your unbeatable deal by 500 Samolians.
你上网能弄到这么好的价钱吗
Stick that in your internet.
-什么 -这家伙太强了 说服我了
- What? - This guy's a bulldog. He wore me down.
别太责怪自己 你根本赢不了我的
Don't be too hard on yourself. You never stood a chance.
谢谢 杰
Thank you, Jay.
上车 我给你演示下操作
Hop in. I'll give you a walk-through.
好的
Okay.
再给点好消息 你的岳父
Some more good news for you -- your father-in-law
还说服我给你装了两年免费的卫星广播
also talked me into two years of free satellite radio.
那是自然 我从来都比不过他
Of course he did. The guy's always one-upping me.
我为了拿到最好的价钱忙了一个月
I work for months getting the best deal.
结果他一来 强势出击
He walks in, bullies you down,
证明了我有多弱
and proves what a pushover I am.
让我给你展示下这个喇叭
Let me just show you this horn.
为什么 他也帮我升级
Why? Did he get an upgrade on --
我岳父也挺贱的 所以我得给你说点事
My father-in-law can be a jerk, too, so I got to say something.
你拿到的价格比他的低太多了
You got a much better deal than he got.
这喇叭不错吧
Some horn, huh?
什么
What?
他到我的办公室来
He came groveling into my office
跪求让我撒个谎
and begged me to lie
让我说他把价格砍得更低
and say that he got the better price,
但他给我补了差价
but he paid me the difference.
他补了多少钱
How much more did he pay?
天啊 他真的好在意我对他的看法
Oh, my God, he really cares what I think about him.
-你没想到吧 -他真是个好人
- More than you know. - That is one beautiful man.
傻蛋 别按喇叭了行不
Hey, dumbass, enough with the horn, huh?
我也爱你
I love you, too!
纹身这东西
Oh! Uh, the tattooing --
真的好疼啊
It does really hurt.
看来我喝得还不够多
I don't think I drank enough.
那今晚还真是开了不少先例
Huh. So, a couple of firsts tonight.
我们该纹什么呢
Okay, what should we get?
要纹对我们有重要意义的图案
It needs to be something important to us.
纳尔逊·曼德拉还在监狱吗
I-is Nelson Mandela still in jail?
应该要纹私人点的比较好吧
I think it should be something just a little more personal.
好吧 那百合怎么样 代表莉莉
Okay, what about lilies for Lily?
花
Flowers?
迫不及待想说我们是弯的吗
Be faster just to get the word "Gay".
大家都准备好了吧 好漂亮啊
I hope everybody's ready! So beautiful.
来看看吧 胆小鬼
Well, check it, losers.
姐纹好了
I am all tatted up.
真为你骄傲 居然真的纹身了
Ay, I'm so proud of you. I can't believe you did this.
-是啊 是啊 是啊 -好性感
- I know! I know! I know! - It's very sexy.
-好好看 -对啊
- Very nice. - Yeah.
梵文里是"母亲"的意思
Well, it is sanskrit for "Mother".
海莉要纹一个"女儿"
And Haley's gonna get one that says "Daughter."
这个嘛
Well...
这个什么
Well, what?
只是
It's just, um,
我不是很确定我会不会临阵退缩
I-I'm not totally sure I'm not bailing.
不会 你不能退缩
No. No, you're not.
可是看上去超痛的
But it just looks super painful,
还有 这跟你无关
a-a-and this is nothing to do with you,
但我不想皮肤皱巴巴的时候有纹身
but I don't think I want a tattoo when I have old skin.
海莉 你不纹"女儿"的话
Haley, if you don't get "Daughter",
这就像是我为我妈纹的
it's gonna look like I did this for my mother,
那样的话我就得把腿锯了
and then I'm gonna have to saw my leg off.
或者你可以再多纹一个词
Or you could just add to it.
梵文的"问题"怎么写
Hey, what's sanskrit for "Issues"?
海莉 快 到你了 纹吧
Haley, come on. You're up. Let's go.
我不想 妈妈
I don't know, mom. It's --
现在看到了 才感觉
Now that I see it,
永远弄不掉的话有点麻烦
it's so permanent.
丫头 我对天发誓我会打你屁屁的
Young lady, I swear to god I will spank you.
我的天 那车是给我的吗
No, my god! Is that for me?!
生日快乐 宝贝
Happy birthday, sweetheart!
太谢谢了 我太喜欢了
Thank you so much! I love it!
千万别告诉我你纹身了
Please tell me you didn't get a tattoo.
没纹 但你要劝下妈妈
No, but talk to mom,
她一直逼我纹
'cause she's trying to make me.
-好酷炫 我能开吗 -当然
- Oh, it's so cute! Can I take it for a ride?! - Of course!
我长大以后 也想有孩子
When I grow up, I want to have kids.
你哪也不许去 晚上喝了酒的
You're not going anywhere. You've been drinking tonight.
还不是你逼我喝的
Only 'cause you made me.
你到底想把她怎么着
What are you trying to do to her?
不过首先 我想有个完美的丈夫
Well, first, I want a perfect husband...
你们呢 快点
How about you guys? Come on.
你们会纹的 对吧
You're gonna get your tattoo, right?
我们发现其实用不着纹身来变酷
We realized we don't need one to be cool.
有点太渴求关注的感觉
It seems sort of desperate.
但是你的纹身很萌
But yours is cute.
-超萌的 -是啊
- Super cute! - Yeah.
一个能照顾我的人
...Someone who takes care of me.
杰 我好累好饿 带我回家吧
Ay, Jay. I'm tired. I'm hungry. Take me home.
走着 给你弄一大碗疯狂朱古力泡芙
Come on. We'll get you a big bowl of Loco-puffs.
然后 我们会生一个宝宝
And then we're gonna make a baby...
好开心
oh, my gosh!
生宝宝很简单的
...Which is easy.
只要把蛋[卵子]和小蝌蚪们
You just put eggs and tadpoles
放在杯子里
in a glass,
让女的喝掉
and the woman has to drink it.
然后 男女亲吻 跳上床
Then, the woman and man kiss and jump on their bed.
一年后 女的尿尿 宝宝就生出来了
After a year, she pees, and a baby comes out.
-我了个去 -我服
- Oh, my god. - Okay, then.
克莱尔纹身了
Now that Claire has a tattoo,
我也终于能纹一个了
I can finally get one of my own!
我一直在想一个
So, I've been trying to think of a phrase
能总结我人生观的金句
that sums up the way I live my life.
我不会鼠目寸光 做事不会虎头蛇尾
I don't think small. I don't do things halfway.
我不怕冒险
I'm not afraid of taking risks.
我也在想一个
So, then, I was trying to think of
最适合纹身的部位
the perfect place to put it, you know?
不能纹在会有皱纹
You don't want to put it on a-a body part
或者下垂太厉害的地方
that's gonna wrinkle or -- or sag too much,
也不能纹在
and you don't want a place where
-穿西装时看得到的地方 -对
- if you wear a suit it will show. - True.
所以 我要在后腰
So, on my lower back,
纹这几个字 "深入"
I would put the words "Go deep,"
"猛上"
"Bang".
-请三思 -我听出来了
- Think about that. - I heard it.
"上" 不行
"Do it". No.
"一起来上"
"All in".